A Guide to the Annual Tax and Operation Reports for Railroads, 1899-1975
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Annual Tax and Operation Reports for Railroads, 1899-1975., Extent: 366 boxes; 165 cubic feet. (Box 1-366)
  - 1910.
    - Hampton Roads Traction Company, 1910 (Box 50)
    - Interstate, 1910 (Box 50)
    - Laurel, 1910 (Box 51)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1910 (Box 51)
    - Lynchburg Belt Line and Connecting, 1910 (Box 51)
    - Lynchburg Traction and Light Company, 1910 (Box 51)
    - Marion and Rye Valley, 1910 (Box 51)
    - Mount Airy and Eastern, 1910 (Box 51)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1910 (Box 51)
    - Newport News and Old Port Royal Railway and Electric Company, 1910 (Box 51)
    - New River, Holston, and Western, 1910 (Box 52)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1910 (Box 52)
    - Norfolk and Atlantic Terminal Company, 1910 (Box 52)
    - Norfolk and Ocean View, 1910 (Box 52)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1910 (Box 52)
    - Newport News and Portsmouth Traction Co., 1910 (Box 52)
    - Norfolk and Southern, 1910 (Box 52)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1910 (Box 52)
    - Norfolk City and Suburban, 1910 (Box 52)
    - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, 1910 (Box 53)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1910 (Box 53)
    - Potomac, 1910 (Box 53)
    - Potomac, Fredericksburg, and Piedmont, 1910 (Box 53)
    - Pocahontas and Western, 1910 (Box 53)
    - Radford Water Power, 1910 (Box 53)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1910 (Box 53)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac and Richmond and Petersburg, 1910 (Box 53)
    - Richmond and Chesapeake Bay, 1910 (Box 53)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1910 (Box 54)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1910 (Box 54)
    - Roaring Fork, 1910 (Box 54)
    - Rossyln Connecting, 1910 (Box 54)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1910 (Box 54)
    - Southern, 1910 (Box 54)
    - Surrey, Sussex, and Southampton, 1910 (Box 54)
    - Tazewell Street, 1910 (Box 54)
    - Tidewater and Western, 1910 (Box 55)
    - Valley, 1910 (Box 55)
    - Virginia Air Line (Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Co. Agt.), 1910 (Box 55)
    - Virginia and Kentucky, 1910 (Box 55)
    - Virginia Southwestern, 1910 (Box 55)
    - Virginia Anthracite Coal, 1910 (Box 55)
    - Virginia - Carolina, 1910 (Box 55)
    - Virginia - Carolina and Southern, 1910 (Box 55)
    - Virginian Terminal, 1910 (Box 56)
    - Virginia Railway and Power Company, 1910 (Box 56)
    - Virginia Southern, 1910 (Box 56)
    - Washington, Alexandria, and Mt. Vernon, 1910 (Box 56)
    - Washington, Arlington, and Falls Church, 1910 (Box 56)
    - Washington Southern, 1910 (Box 56)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1910 (Box 56)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1910 (Box 56)
    - Wise Terminal, 1910 (Box 56)
  - 1911.
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1911 (Box 57)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1911 (Box 57)
    - Big Sandy and Cumberland, 1911 (Box 57)
    - Big Stone Gap and Powell's Valley, 1911 (Box 57)
    - Blue Ridge Light and Power Company, 1911 (Box 57)
    - Bluestone Traction, 1911 (Box 57)
    - Cape Charles, 1911 (Box 57)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1911 (Box 57)
    - Charlottesville and Albemarle, 1911 (Box 57)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio (2 folders), 1911 (Box 58)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1911 (Box 58)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1911 (Box 58)
    - Citizens Railway, Light, and Power Company, 1911 (Box 58)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1911 (Box 58)
    - Danville Railway and Electric Company, 1911 (Box 58)
    - Danville Western, 1911 (Box 58)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1911 (Box 58)
    - Elkhorn Southern, 1911 (Box 59)
    - Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1911 (Box 59)
    - Great Falls and Old Dominion, 1911 (Box 59)
    - Hampton Roads Traction Company, 1911 (Box 59)
    - Interstate, 1911 (Box 59)
    - Interstate, 1911 (Box 59)
    - Laurel, 1911 (Box 59)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1911 (Box 59)
    - Lynchburg Traction and Light, 1911 (Box 59)
    - Marion and Rye Valley, 1911 (Box 60)
    - Mill Mountain Incline, 1911 (Box 60)
    - Mount Airy and Eastern, 1911 (Box 60)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1911 (Box 60)
    - Newport News, and Old Point Comfort Railway and Electric Co., 1911 (Box 60)
    - New River, Holston, and Western, 1911 (Box 60)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1911 (Box 60)
    - Norfolk and Atlantic Terminal Company, 1911 (Box 60)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Traction Company, 1911 (Box 60)
    - Norfolk and Ocean View, 1911 (Box 61)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1911 (Box 61)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1911 (Box 61)
    - Norfolk City and Suburban, 1911 (Box 61)
    - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, 1911 (Box 61)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1911 (Box 61)
    - Potomac, 1911 (Box 61)
    - Potomac, Fredericksburg, and Piedmont, 1911 (Box 61)
    - Radford Water Power Company, 1911 (Box 61)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1911 (Box 62)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac and Richmond and Petersburg Railway Connection Company, 1911 (Box 62)
    - Richmond and Chesapeake Bay, 1911 (Box 62)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1911 (Box 62)
    - Roaring Fork, 1911 (Box 62)
    - Rossyln Connecting, 1911 (Box 62)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1911 (Box 62)
    - Southern, 1911 (Box 63)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1911 (Box 63)
    - Tazewell Street, 1911 (Box 63)
    - Tidewater and Western, 1911 (Box 63)
    - Valley, 1911 (Box 63)
    - Virginia Air Line, 1911 (Box 63)
    - Virginia and Kentucky, 1911 (Box 63)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1911 (Box 63)
    - Virginia Anthracite Coal, 1911 (Box 64)
    - Virginia - Carolina, 1911 (Box 64)
    - Virginia - Carolina and Southern, 1911 (Box 64)
    - Virginian, 1911 (Box 64)
    - Virginian Terminal, 1911 (Box 64)
    - Virginia Railway and Power Company, 1911 (Box 64)
    - Virginia Southern, 1911 (Box 64)
    - Washington, Alexandria, and Mt. Vernon, 1911 (Box 64)
    - Washington, Arlington, and Falls Church, 1911 (Box 65)
    - Washington Southern, 1911 (Box 65)
    - Washington - Virginia, 1911 (Box 65)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1911 (Box 65)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1911 (Box 65)
    - Wise Terminal, 1911 (Box 65)
  - 1912.
    - Atlantic and Danville (2 folders), 1912 (Box 65)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1912 (Box 66)
    - Appalachian Power Company, 1912 (Box 66)
    - Big Sandy and Cumberland, 1912 (Box 66)
    - Big Stone Gap and Powell's Valley (2 folders), 1912 (Box 66)
    - Blue Ridge Light and Power, 1912 (Box 66)
    - Cape Charles, 1912 (Box 66)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1912 (Box 66)
    - Charlottesville and Albemarle, 1912 (Box 66)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio (2 folders), 1912 (Box 67)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1912 (Box 67)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1912 (Box 67)
    - Citizens Railway Light and Power Company, 1912 (Box 67)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1912 (Box 67)
    - Danville and Western, 1912 (Box 67)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1912 (Box 67)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1912 (Box 68)
    - Elkhorn Southern, 1912 (Box 68)
    - Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1912 (Box 68)
    - Hampton Roads Traction Company, 1912 (Box 68)
    - Interstate, 1912 (Box 68)
    - Laurel, 1912 (Box 68)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1912 (Box 68)
    - Lynchburg Traction and Light Company, 1912 (Box 68)
    - Marion and Rye Valley, 1912 (Box 69)
    - Mill Mountain Incline Incorporated, 1912 (Box 69)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1912 (Box 69)
    - Newport News, and Old Point Railway and Electric Company, 1912 (Box 69)
    - New River, Holston, and Western, 1912 (Box 69)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1912 (Box 69)
    - Norfolk and Ocean View, 1912 (Box 69)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1912 (Box 69)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1912 (Box 70)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1912 (Box 70)
    - Norfolk City and Suburban, 1912 (Box 70)
    - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, 1912 (Box 70)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1912 (Box 70)
    - Potomac, 1912 (Box 70)
    - Potomac, Fredericksburg, and Piedmont, 1912 (Box 70)
    - Radford Water Power Company, 1912 (Box 70)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac (2 folders), 1912 (Box 71)
    - Richmond and Henrico, 1912 (Box 71)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1912 (Box 71)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1912 (Box 71)
    - Roaring Fork, 1912 (Box 71)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1912 (Box 71)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1912 (Box 71)
    - Southern, 1912 (Box 72)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1912 (Box 72)
    - Tazewell Street, 1912 (Box 72)
    - Terminal, 1912 (Box 72)
    - Tidewater and Western, 1912 (Box 72)
    - Valley, 1912 (Box 72)
    - Virginia Air Line, 1912 (Box 72)
    - Virginia and Kentucky, 1912 (Box 72)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1912 (Box 73)
    - Virginia - Carolina, 1912 (Box 73)
    - Virginia - Carolina and Southern, 1912 (Box 73)
    - Virginian, 1912 (Box 73)
    - Virginia Railway and Power Company, 1912 (Box 73)
    - Virginia Southern, 1912 (Box 73)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1912 (Box 73)
    - Washington Southern, 1912 (Box 73)
    - Washington Utilities, 1912 (Box 74)
    - Washington - Virginia, 1912 (Box 74)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1912 (Box 74)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1912 (Box 74)
    - Wise Terminal, 1912 (Box 74)
  - 1913.
    - Appalachian Power Company, 1913 (Box 74)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1913 (Box 74)
    - Big Sandy and Cumberland, 1913 (Box 74)
    - Big Stone Gap and Powell's Valley, 1913 (Box 75)
    - Blue Ridge Light and Power Company, 1913 (Box 75)
    - Cape Charles, 1913 (Box 75)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1913 (Box 75)
    - Charlottesville and Albemarle, 1913 (Box 75)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1913 (Box 75)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1913 (Box 75)
    - Citizens Railway Light and Power Company, 1913 (Box 75)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1913 (Box 75)
    - Danville and Western, 1913 (Box 76)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1913 (Box 76)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1913 (Box 76)
    - Electric Railroad Norfolk Southern Railroad Company, 1913 (Box 76)
    - Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1913 (Box 76)
    - Hampton Roads Traction Company, 1913 (Box 76)
    - Interstate, 1913 (Box 76)
    - Laurel, 1913 (Box 76)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1913 (Box 77)
    - Lynchburg Traction and Light, 1913 (Box 77)
    - Marion and Rye Valley, 1913 (Box 77)
    - Mill Mountain Incline Incorporated, 1913 (Box 77)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1913 (Box 77)
    - Newport News, and Old Point Railway and Electric Company, 1913 (Box 77)
    - New River, Holston, and Western, 1913 (Box 77)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1913 (Box 77)
    - Norfolk and Ocean View, 1913 (Box 78)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1913 (Box 78)
    - Norfolk City and Suburban, 1913 (Box 78)
    - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, 1913 (Box 78)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1913 (Box 78)
    - Norfolk Terminal (2 folders), 1913 (Box 78)
    - Potomac, 1913 (Box 78)
    - Potomac, Fredericksburg, and Piedmont, 1913 (Box 78)
    - Radford Water Power Company, 1913 (Box 79)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1913 (Box 79)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac and Richmond and Petersburg Connecting, 1913 (Box 79)
    - Richmond and Chesapeake Bay, 1913 (Box 79)
    - Richmond and Henrico, 1913 (Box 79)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1913 (Box 79)
    - Richmond and Rappahanock, 1913 (Box 79)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Co., 1913 (Box 79)
    - Roaring Fork, 1913 (Box 79)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1913 (Box 80)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1913 (Box 80)
    - Southern, 1913 (Box 80)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1913 (Box 80)
    - Tazewell Street 1913 (Box 80)
    - Tidewater and Western, 1913 (Box 80)
    - Valley, 1913 (Box 80)
    - Virginia and Kentucky, 1913 (Box 80)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1913 (Box 81)
    - Virginia - Carolina, 1913 (Box 81)
    - Virginian, 1913 (Box 81)
    - Virginian Terminal, 1913 (Box 81)
    - Virginia Railway and Power Company, 1913 (Box 81)
    - Virginia Southern, 1913 (Box 81)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1913 (Box 81)
    - Washington Southern, 1913 (Box 81)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1913 (Box 82)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1913 (Box 82)
  - 1914.
    - Appalachian Power Company, 1914 (Box 82)
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1914 (Box 82)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1914 (Box 82)
    - Big Sandy and Cumberland, 1914 (Box 82)
    - Big Stone Gap and Powell's Valley, 1914 (Box 82)
    - Blue Ridge Light and Power Company, 1914 (Box 82)
    - Cape Charles, 1914 (Box 82)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1914 (Box 83)
    - Charlottesville and Albemarle, 1914 (Box 83)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1914 (Box 83)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1914 (Box 83)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1914 (Box 83)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1914 (Box 83)
    - Danville and Western, 1914 (Box 83)
    - Danville Traction Power Company, 1914 (Box 83)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1914 (Box 83)
    - Electric, 1914 (Box 84)
    - Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1914 (Box 84)
    - Interstate, 1914 (Box 84)
    - Laurel, 1914 (Box 84)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1914 (Box 84)
    - Lynchburg Traction Light Company, 1914 (Box 84)
    - Marion and Rye Valley, 1914 (Box 84)
    - Mill Mountain Incline Incorporated, 1914 (Box 84)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1914 (Box 84)
    - Newport News and Hampton Railway, Gas and Electric Company, 1914 (Box 85)
    - New River, Holston, and Western, 1914 (Box 85)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1914 (Box 85)
    - Norfolk and Ocean View, 1914 (Box 85)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1914 (Box 85)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1914 (Box 85)
    - Norfolk City and Suburban, 1914 (Box 85)
    - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, 1914 (Box 85)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1914 (Box 85)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1914 (Box 85)
    - Potomac, 1914 (Box 86)
    - Potomac, Fredericksburg, and Piedmont, 1914 (Box 86)
    - Radford Water Power Company, 1914 (Box 86)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1914 (Box 86)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac and Richmond and Petersburg, 1914 (Box 86)
    - Richmond and Chesapeake Bay, 1914 (Box 86)
    - Richmond and Henrico, 1914 (Box 86)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1914 (Box 86)
    - Richmond and Rappahannock, 1914 (Box 86)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric, 1914 (Box 87)
    - Roaring Fork, 1914 (Box 87)
    - Rossyln Connecting, 1914 (Box 87)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1914 (Box 87)
    - Southern, 1914 (Box 87)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1914 (Box 87)
    - Tazewell Street, 1914 (Box 87)
    - Tidewater and Western, 1914 (Box 87)
    - Valley, 1914 (Box 87)
    - Virginia and Kentucky, 1914 (Box 88)
    - Virginia and Southern, 1914 (Box 88)
    - Virginia - Carolina, 1914 (Box 88)
    - Virginian, 1914 (Box 88)
    - Virginian Terminal, 1914 (Box 88)
    - Virginia Railway and Power Company, 1914 (Box 88)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1914 (Box 88)
    - Washington Southern, 1914 (Box 88)
    - Washington Utilities, 1914 (Box 89)
    - Washington - Virginia, 1914 (Box 89)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1914 (Box 89)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1914 (Box 89)
  - 1915.
    - Appalachian Power Co., 1915 (Box 89)
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1915 (Box 89)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1915 (Box 89)
    - Big Stone Gap and Powell's Valley, 1915 (Box 89)
    - Blue Ridge Light and Power Company, 1915 (Box 89)
    - Cape Charles, 1915 (Box 90)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1915 (Box 90)
    - Charlottesville and Albemarle, 1915 (Box 90)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1915 (Box 90)
    - Chesapeake and Western, 1915 (Box 90)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1915 (Box 90)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1915 (Box 90)
    - Danville and Western, 1915 (Box 90)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1915 (Box 90)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1915 (Box 91)
    - Franklin and Pittsylvania, 1915 (Box 91)
    - Interstate, 1915 (Box 91)
    - Laurel, 1915 (Box 91)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1915 (Box 91)
    - Lynchburg Traction and Light Company, 1915 (Box 91)
    - Marion and Rye Valley, 1915 (Box 91)
    - Mill Mountain Incline Incorporated, 1915 (Box 91)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1915 (Box 92)
    - Newport News and Hampton Railways, Gas and Electric Company, 1915 (Box 92)
    - New River, Holston, and Western, 1915 (Box 92)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1915 (Box 92)
    - Norfolk and Ocean View, 1915 (Box 92)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1915 (Box 92)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1915 (Box 92)
    - Norfolk City and Suburban, 1915 (Box 92)
    - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, 1915 (Box 92)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1915 (Box 92)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1915 (Box 93)
    - Potomac, 1915 (Box 93)
    - Potomac, Fredericksburg, and Piedmont, 1915 (Box 93)
    - Radford Water Power Company, 1915 (Box 93)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1915 (Box 93)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac and Richmond and Petersburg, 1915 (Box 93)
    - Richmond and Chesapeake Bay, 1915 (Box 93)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1915 (Box 93)
    - Richmond and Rappahannock, 1915 (Box 93)
    - Richmond Railway and Viaduct Company, 1915 (Box 93)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1915 (Box 94)
    - Roaring Fork, 1915 (Box 94)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1915 (Box 94)
    - Seaboard Air Line (2 folders), 1915 (Box 94)
    - Southern, 1915 (Box 94)
    - Surry, Sussex, and Southampton, 1915 (Box 94)
    - Tazewell Street, 1915 (Box 94)
    - Valley, 1915 (Box 94)
    - Virginia and Kentucky, 1915 (Box 95)
    - Virginia and Southwestern, 1915 (Box 95)
    - Virginia - Carolina, 1915 (Box 95)
    - Virginian 1915 (Box 95)
    - Virginian Terminal, 1915 (Box 95)
    - Virginia Railway and Power Company, 1915 (Box 95)
    - Virginia Southern, 1915 (Box 95)
    - Washington and Old Dominion, 1915 (Box 95)
    - Washington Southern, 1915 (Box 95)
    - Washington - Virginia, 1915 (Box 96)
    - Winchester and Potomac, 1915 (Box 96)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1915 (Box 96)
  - 1916.
    - Appalachian Power Company (2 folders), 1916 (Box 96)
    - Atlantic and Danville (2 folders), 1916 (Box 96)
    - Atlantic Coast Line (2 folders), 1915 (Box 96)
    - Big Sandy and Cumberland (3 folders), 1916 (Box 97)
    - Big Stone Gap and Powell's Valley, 1916 (Box 97)
    - Blue Ridge Light and Power (2 folders), 1916 (Box 97)
    - Cape Charles (2 folders), 1916 (Box 97)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio (2 folders), 1916 (Box 97)
    - Charlottesville and Albemarle, 1916 (Box 97)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1916 (Box 97)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1916 (Box 98)
    - Chesapeake and Western (2 folders), 1916 (Box 98)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg (2 folders), 1916 (Box 98)
    - Danville and Western (2 folders), 1916 (Box 98)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company (2 folders), 1916 (Box 98)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia (2 folders), 1916 (Box 98)
    - Interstate (2 folders), 1916 (Box 99)
    - Laurel (2 folders), 1916 (Box 99)
    - Louisville and Nashville (2 folders), 1916 (Box 99)
    - Lynchburg Traction and Light Company (2 folders), 1916 (Box 99)
    - Marion and Rye Valley (2 folders), 1916 (Box 99)
    - Mill Mountain Incline Incorporated (2 folders), 1916 (Box 99)
    - Nelson and Albemarle (2 folders), 1916 (Box 100)
    - Newport News and Hampton Railway, Gas and Electric (2 folders), 1916 (Box 100)
    - New River, Holston, and Western, 1916 (Box 100)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk (2 folders), 1916 (Box 100)
    - Norfolk and Ocean View (2 folders), 1916 (Box 100)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line (2 folders), 1916 (Box 100)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1916 (Box 100)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1916 (Box 101)
    - Norfolk City and Suburban (2 folders), 1916 (Box 101)
    - Norfolk Railway and Light Company (2 folders), 1916 (Box 101)
    - Norfolk Southern (2 folders), 1916 (Box 101)
    - Norfolk Terminal (2 folders), 1916 (Box 101)
    - Petersburg and Appomattox (2 folders), 1916 (Box 101)
    - Potomac (2 folders), 1916 (Box 102)
    - Potomac, Fredericksburg, and Piedmont (2 folders), 1916 (Box 102)
    - Radford Water Power Company (2 folders), 1916 (Box 102)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac, 1916 (Box 102)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac and Richmond and Petersburg (2 folders), 1916 (Box 102)
    - Richmond and Chesapeake Bay (2 folders), 1916 (Box 102)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg (2 folders), 1916 (Box 102)
    - Richmond and Rappahannock (2 folders), 1916 (Box 102)
    - Richmond Railway and Viaduct Company, 1916 (Box 102)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1916 (Box 102)
    - Roaring Fork, 1916 (Box 102)
    - Rosslyn Connecting (2 folders), 1916 (Box 103)
    - Seaboard Air Line (2 folders), 1916 (Box 103)
    - Southern (2 folders), 1916 (Box 103)
    - Surrey, Sussex, and Southampton, 1916 (Box 103)
    - Tazewell Street (2 folders), 1916 (Box 103)
    - Tidewater and Western, 1916 (Box 103)
    - Tidewater and Western, 1916 (Box 104)
    - Valley (2 folders), 1916 (Box 104)
    - Virginia and Kentucky, 1916 (Box 104)
    - Virginia and Southwestern (2 folders), 1916 (Box 104)
    - Virginia Blue Ridge (2 folders), 1916 (Box 104)
    - Virginia - Carolina (2 folders), 1916 (Box 104)
    - Virginian, 1916 (Box 104)
    - Virginian, 1916 (Box 105)
    - Virginia Railway and Power Company (2 folders), 1916 (Box 105)
    - Virginia Southern (2 folders), 1916 (Box 105)
    - Washington and Old Dominion (2 folders), 1916 (Box 105)
    - Washington Southern, 1916 (Box 105)
    - Washington - Virginia (2 folders), 1916 (Box 105)
    - Winchester Virginia (2 folders), 1916 (Box 105)
    - Winchester and Strasburg, 1916 (Box 106)
  - 1917.
    - Appalachian Power Company, 1917 (Box 106)
    - Atlantic and Danville, 1917 (Box 106)
    - Atlantic Coast Line, 1917 (Box 106)
    - Blue Ridge Light and Power Company, 1917 (Box 106)
    - Big Sandy and Cumberland, 1917 (Box 106)
    - Cape Charles, 1917 (Box 106)
    - Carolina, Clinchfield, and Ohio, 1917 (Box 106)
    - Charlottesville and Albemarle, 1917 (Box 107)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1917 (Box 107)
    - Chesapeake and Western (3 folders), 1917 (Box 107)
    - Chesapeake Western, 1917 (Box 107)
    - Cumberland Valley and Martinsburg, 1917 (Box 107)
    - Danville Traction and Power Company, 1917 (Box 107)
    - Danville and Western, 1917 (Box 107)
    - Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia, 1917 (Box 107)
    - Franklin and Pittsylvania (3 folders), 1917 (Box 107)
    - Hampton and Langley Field, 1917 (Box 107)
    - Hopewell and City Point, 1917 (Box 107)
    - Interstate, 1917 (Box 108)
    - Louisville and Nashville, 1917 (Box 108)
    - Lynchburg Traction and Light Company, 1917 (Box 108)
    - Mill Mountain Incline Incorporated, 1917 (Box 108)
    - Nelson and Albemarle, 1917 (Box 108)
    - Newport News and Hampton Railway, Gas and Electric, 1917 (Box 108)
    - New River, Holston, and Western, 1917 (Box 108)
    - New York, Philadelphia, and Norfolk, 1917 (Box 108)
    - Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line, 1917 (Box 108)
    - Norfolk and Western, 1917 (Box 109)
    - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, 1917 (Box 109)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1917 (Box 109)
    - Norfolk Terminal, 1917 (Box 109)
    - Norton and Northern (2 folders), 1917 (Box 109)
    - Petersburg and Appomattox, 1917 (Box 109)
    - Radford Water Power Company, 1917 (Box 109)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac (2 folders), 1917 (Box 109)
    - Richmond and Mecklenburg, 1917 (Box 109)
    - Roanoke Railway and Electric Company, 1917 (Box 109)
    - Roaring Fork, 1917 (Box 109)
    - Rosslyn Connecting, 1917 (Box 109)
    - Seaboard Air Line, 1917 (Box 110)